<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Meet the Team on Introduction to Scientific Research</title>
    <link>https://ci15.netlify.app/people/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Meet the Team on Introduction to Scientific Research</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Laboratoire ERPI - UL</copyright><atom:link href="https://ci15.netlify.app/people/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Garrick Aden-Buie</title>
      <link>https://ci15.netlify.app/people/garrick/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ci15.netlify.app/people/garrick/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m a Data Science Educator and R developer for RStudio. I use R, R Markdown, Shiny, and the tools of data science to make it easier to teach and learn data science with R, primarily through my work supporting the learnr and gradethis packages.
I am passionate about making great-looking, interactive presentations with R Markdown and the xaringan. I&amp;rsquo;ve created two packages that help you take your slides to the next level:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Silvia Canelón</title>
      <link>https://ci15.netlify.app/people/silvia/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ci15.netlify.app/people/silvia/</guid>
      <description>I am a researcher, community organizer, and R educator. My research leverages electronic health record data to study pregnancy-related outcomes, and my organizing values data literacy as a way to build power and effect change.
I enjoy finding ways to communicate technical knowledge with a variety of audiences and love showing others how to leverage xaringan to create effective, reproducible, and beautiful presentations. I have taught xaringan workshops in both English and Spanish to R users across disciplines:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Patricia Loto</title>
      <link>https://ci15.netlify.app/people/patricia/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ci15.netlify.app/people/patricia/</guid>
      <description>I have a B.S. in I.T. and a Diploma in Data Sciences, Machine Learning and its Applications. I work as a software developer and data analyst at the government agency for lotteries and casinos of the province of Chaco in Argentina.
Part of the Metadocencia Accessibility team.
Co-organizer of R-Ladies Resistencia-Corrientes and Instructor of Carpintería Software (Software Carpentry).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Shannon Pileggi</title>
      <link>https://ci15.netlify.app/people/shannon/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ci15.netlify.app/people/shannon/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m currently a Statistician at Adelphi Research in Doylestown, PA working in pharmaceutical market research; previously, I was an Assistant Professor of Statistics at California Polytechnic State University, San Luis Obispo.
My day-to-day in R include: fine-tuning ggplots to convey analysis results, contributing to an internal package to automate analyses, and developing shiny aps.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
