<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Meet the Team on Introduction to Scientific Research</title>
    <link>https://ci15.netlify.app/people/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Meet the Team on Introduction to Scientific Research</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Laboratoire ERPI - UL</copyright><atom:link href="https://ci15.netlify.app/people/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Fabio A. Cruz Sanchez</title>
      <link>https://ci15.netlify.app/people/fabio/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ci15.netlify.app/people/fabio/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ferney Osorio</title>
      <link>https://ci15.netlify.app/people/ferney/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ci15.netlify.app/people/ferney/</guid>
      <description>I am a passionate facilitator of collaborative work and collective intelligence from Colombia. My expertise is focused on the design and management of innovation labs, particularly the strategic management and facilitation of collaborative innovation processes involving public-private-people partnerships.
He is an electronics engineer of the Universidad Nacional de Colombia (UNAL). He received his MSc on a double degree program on Industrial Engineering and Innovation Management from Université de Lorraine (UL) and UNAL.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Alex Gabriel</title>
      <link>https://ci15.netlify.app/people/alex/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ci15.netlify.app/people/alex/</guid>
      <description>Engineer and doctor in industrial engineering, my professional and research experiences are mainly focused on the digital tools of the different steps of the innovation and creativity process. I address the issues of preparation of the ideation phase, capitalization of knowledge from ideation to prototyping, visualization and prototyping of concepts.
I am interested in artificial intelligence technologies (ontology, machine learning, neural networks, optimization &amp;hellip;). I did my thesis in collaboration with Polytechnique Montréal on knowledge management during the collaborative process of creativity.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mauricio Camargo</title>
      <link>https://ci15.netlify.app/people/mauricio/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ci15.netlify.app/people/mauricio/</guid>
      <description>Mauricio Camargo is full professor on Management of Technology and Innovation at the Ecole Nationale en Génie des Systèmes Industriels of Nancy (The Industrial Engineering School of the University of Lorraine -France), and researcher at the ERPI Laboratory (Research team on Innovative processes). BSc. On Chemical Engineering Universidad Nacional de Colombia. PhD on Automatics of Industrial and Human systems form the Université de Valenciennes et de Hainaut Cambresis in France. His main research interests are; New Product Development, decision making in innovation processes and technology strategy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Giovanny Arbelaez</title>
      <link>https://ci15.netlify.app/people/gio/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ci15.netlify.app/people/gio/</guid>
      <description>Engineer and PhD. I am a researcher that is passionate about human-centered design methods, innovation, technology and coffee (yes coffee!).
I have been interested in stakeholder&amp;rsquo;s and user&amp;rsquo;s integration during the entire design cycle as a way to improve a product&amp;rsquo;s acceptability. Uncovering the need for tools to help designers and engineers to evaluate and measure the product&amp;rsquo;s acceptability, I developed a method to estimate it early in the design process.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
