<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Introduction to Scientific Research</title>
    <link>https://ci15.netlify.app/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Introduction to Scientific Research</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Laboratoire ERPI - UL</copyright><atom:link href="https://ci15.netlify.app/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Garrick Aden-Buie</title>
      <link>https://ci15.netlify.app/people/garrick/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ci15.netlify.app/people/garrick/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m a Data Science Educator and R developer for RStudio. I use R, R Markdown, Shiny, and the tools of data science to make it easier to teach and learn data science with R, primarily through my work supporting the learnr and gradethis packages.
I am passionate about making great-looking, interactive presentations with R Markdown and the xaringan. I&amp;rsquo;ve created two packages that help you take your slides to the next level:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Silvia Canelón</title>
      <link>https://ci15.netlify.app/people/silvia/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ci15.netlify.app/people/silvia/</guid>
      <description>I am a researcher, community organizer, and R educator. My research leverages electronic health record data to study pregnancy-related outcomes, and my organizing values data literacy as a way to build power and effect change.
I enjoy finding ways to communicate technical knowledge with a variety of audiences and love showing others how to leverage xaringan to create effective, reproducible, and beautiful presentations. I have taught xaringan workshops in both English and Spanish to R users across disciplines:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Patricia Loto</title>
      <link>https://ci15.netlify.app/people/patricia/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ci15.netlify.app/people/patricia/</guid>
      <description>I have a B.S. in I.T. and a Diploma in Data Sciences, Machine Learning and its Applications. I work as a software developer and data analyst at the government agency for lotteries and casinos of the province of Chaco in Argentina.
Part of the Metadocencia Accessibility team.
Co-organizer of R-Ladies Resistencia-Corrientes and Instructor of Carpintería Software (Software Carpentry).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Shannon Pileggi</title>
      <link>https://ci15.netlify.app/people/shannon/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ci15.netlify.app/people/shannon/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m currently a Statistician at Adelphi Research in Doylestown, PA working in pharmaceutical market research; previously, I was an Assistant Professor of Statistics at California Polytechnic State University, San Luis Obispo.
My day-to-day in R include: fine-tuning ggplots to convey analysis results, contributing to an internal package to automate analyses, and developing shiny aps.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Code of Conduct</title>
      <link>https://ci15.netlify.app/code-of-conduct/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ci15.netlify.app/code-of-conduct/</guid>
      <description>Everyone involved in this tutorial &amp;mdash; either as an instructor, TA, or particpant &amp;mdash; agrees to abide by the useR!2021 Code of Conduct, repeated below in full.
If you notice someone in distress, observe unacceptable behavior, or have concerns you would like to discuss, please reach out to Garrick Aden-Buie or Silvia Canelón via private message during the tutorial. Alternatively, you may email the useR!2021 Code of Conduct Response Team at useR2021-coc [at] r-project.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contributors</title>
      <link>https://ci15.netlify.app/contributors/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ci15.netlify.app/contributors/</guid>
      <description>Thank you to all the folks who have contributed both technical and creative skills to this project:
   Desirée De Leon 🦒 (designed 5 of the custom color themes, made illustrations for the workshop, and provided general aesthetic feedback along the way)
   Garrick Aden-Buie 🧙‍♀️ (debugged headroom.js and lent his panelset.js code to the theme)
   Allison Horst 🐕 (awesome illustrations of campfires, seedlings, and evergreens, as well as my R Markdown hedgehog mascot 🦔)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>License</title>
      <link>https://ci15.netlify.app/license/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ci15.netlify.app/license/</guid>
      <description>The materials for this tutorial are released under a Creative Commons Attribution-ShareAlike 4.0 International License.
  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Slides</title>
      <link>https://ci15.netlify.app/slides/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ci15.netlify.app/slides/</guid>
      <description>Please see each set of slides in context in the Materials page.
  01-introduction   02-style-guide   03-xaringan-extras   04-effective-communication   05-accessible-design   06-intro-css   07-accessibility-css-html   08-more-css   09-design-components   break   thanks   </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
